https://www.visitcaymanislands.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Leisure Travel Update
As of October 1, 2020, the Cayman Islands commenced the phased opening of its international borders. Leisure travel is not allowed in this phase which focuses on repatriation flights and returning residents/homeowners. For the latest information on how to travel safely and responsibly to the Cayman Islands, please click HERE.
Global Citizen Concierge
Apply now to become a Global Citizen and trade in your WFH routine for sun, sand, sea and safety in Cayman for up to two years.
See Details
Home > Privacy Policy
The Cayman Islands Department of Tourism (CIDOT) operates this website. CIDOT respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your Personal Data. This privacy notice will inform you as to how we look after your Personal Data when you visit this website (“Website”) and interact with us online – regardless of where you visit from – and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.
The Website is designed to inform you about our beautiful islands. Only in a few places on our Website we ask you for your Personal Data in order to be able to offer you certain services, e.g. the newsletter or contact us. You may also use the Website without disclosing or otherwise leaving any Personal Data to us, especially if you deactivate cookies and do not communicate with us via the Website.
If you would like to know more about how we handle your Personal Data, please read the Privacy Policy - Long Version.
On this website, we use cookies to enhance your user experience, improve our website and provide you with personalized marketing. Please see our Privacy Policy to learn more. You can also Manage Your Cookie Settings.
